Guide to the Medical Center records, 1825-2005 RG0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs and negatives, 1943-1987; RG0007 Series 7; 1 Linear foot (Box 1, Box 2)
  - News Conference about Pres. Reagan at GW Hospital, 03/30/1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Arman kicks off a football, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Robert I. Keimowitz, Ass. Dean for Student Affairs and Admissions, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Robert I. Keimowitz, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Hospital Room, Columbian University Hospital, H Street, circa 1890 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Surgery and Class Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Follies II, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - William Cline Borden, Dean of Medical School 1909-1931, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Medical Alumni Pres. Jerome W. Canter, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Commencement and President's Tea, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - David H. Winston receives diploma from GW School of Medicine, 03/28/1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Dean Parks, L. Yochelson, J.E. Rankin, and E.K. Morris, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - William R. Merriam visits Dr. Stevens, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Dr. Louis Kazlaff, Cancer Clinic, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Drs. Zimmerman and Ticktin, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dr. James Sites, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Merit Award presented to Dr. Donald H. Stubbs' daughter, Peggy Ann, 02/1956 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Twin Griffiths and Liebler, 10/1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Includes two photographs
  - AOA lecture, Prof. Roe and Dr. Vallee, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Commencement and President's Tea, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Medical Society Banquet, Mayflower Hotel, 04/04/1956 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Planning session, 03/1951 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Micro-isolation apparatus demonstration, 03/1952 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - J. Edgar Hoover presents check to GW Pres., 02/29/1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - GW Pres. Marvin reads citation to Med. School, 10/01/1954 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dedication of the School of Medicine, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Mr. Gill presents gift to GW, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Alumni of Class of 1927, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Luther Rice Award recipient, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Turkish flag preented to GW chapter of the Student American Medical Assoc., 06/28/1955 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Drs. Epstein and Kaiser, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Opening assembly, School of Medicine, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Med. Students at NIH, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Drs. Samuel Dodek and John Parks, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Dr. Alec Horwitz, Clinical Surgery Professor, 06/1960 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Physician at work, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Commencement, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Hippies' Medical Counselors, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Commencement, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Commencement, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Dr. Brian Blades and Alva McIva Griffith, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Drs. J. Adams and Yochelson, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - War times photo, Medical School, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Commencement and President's Tea, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Dr. Paul Calabrisi, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Drs. McKelway and Titus, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Alice Martinson wins Navy commission, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Medical school opening, 10/1949 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Warburg apparatus, 03/1952 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Drs. Pierpont and Calatayud, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Drs. A. Parrish and Zimmerman, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Follies II, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    Negative only; Photos without original numbering
  - Medical students, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Dr. Keimowitz, 08/24/1978 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Medical Class Columbian University, 1895; Series 7 (Map-folder 1)
- Reports, 1991-1995; RG0007 Series 8; 3 Linear feet
  This series consists of nursing reports, mortality reports, JCAHO survey notes, DCRA reports,. The materials range in date from 1991-95.
- Statistics of medical school, 1943-1969; RG0007 Series 9; 1 Linear foot (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of statistics of medical school entering students, including acceptances, denials, withdrawals, geographic distribution, age ranges, colleges attended, reports to committee on admissions, etc. The materials range in date from 1934-69.
- Women's Board, 1990-1999; RG0007 Series 10; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of historical files, correspondence, minutes, reports, etc. of the hospital Women's Board. The materials range in date from 1990-99.
  - Medical Center - Women's Board, 1898-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Women's Board - History, Interviews, etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Women's Board - File of President Mrs. T. Taylor Perry (Jo Ellen) - Re: Monthly meetings (partial), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Women's Board - File of President Mrs. Robert L. (Dorothy) Tull, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Women's Board - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Women's Board (binder) - Minutes, New Members, Gift Shop, Newsletter, etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Also includes Sommer Student Award, Library Cart, Bazaar, Treasurer's Reports, History, Publicity
- Committee files, 1984-1996; RG0007 Series 11; 9 Linear feet
  This series consists of medical staff committee by-laws, minutes, committee records, board of trustees. The materials range in date from 1984-96.
- Inactive physicians files, 1949-1997; RG0007 Series 12; 16.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of inactive physicians files from medical staff office, and range in date from 1949-97.
  - Aaron, Benjamin, 03/20/1980 -10/01/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Department: Sugery
  - Abramson, Randi C., 02/10/1993 -03/29/1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Department: Medicine
  - Adams, Margaret Rode, 10/27/1994 -01/31/1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adi, Marwa, 05/18/1989 -07/16/1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Department: Ophthalmology
  - Akerele, Flavrus A., 01/17/1985 -04/18/1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alarcon, Julio E., 09/25/1972 -06/06/1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alkan, Serhan, 10/26/1995 -02/19/1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    epartment: Pathology
  - Alper, Melvin Gustavus, 09/10/1954 -09/18/1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alter, Israel, 09/17/1984 -12/02/1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anaise, David, 02/10/1994 -02/04/1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Department: Surgery
  - Ardam, Irwin H., 05/23/1960 -06/03/1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    epartment: Internal Medicine
  - Armaly, Mansour, 09/21/1970 -12/31/1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Barnard, Neal, 10/20/1983 -03/31/1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Department: Psychiatry
  - Belaval, Gustavo S., 06/19/1978 -01/10/1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Berry, Zail S., 03/19/1992 -09/23/1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Department: Health Care Services
  - Billeti, Sanford, 09/16/1974 -07/03/1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bland, Louis H., 09/20/1982 -11/30/1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Blumen, Helen E., 10/26/1995 -06/18/1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Blunda, Michael, 10/20/1991 -03/06/1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Boldt, Leigh S., 10/27/1994 -06/28/1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bono, Vincent H., 05/17/1990 -03/17/1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Borenstein, David G., 06/19/1978 -10/31/1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bradley. Robert L., 10/26/1995 -05/23/1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Braun, Alien R., 10/11/1990 -03/03/1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Department: Neurology
  - Breslin, Nancy A., 10/16/1986 -06/30/1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Broome, Catherine M., 10/17/1991 -03/15/1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Campbell, Lynn R., 08/16/1995 -07/01/1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chae, Frank, 07/01/1996 -06/30/1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chaffee, Melissa, 01/26/1991 -03/17/1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Charya, Sampath, 10/06/1996 -07/01/1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chen, Anita, 05/16/1996 -07/30/1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chucker, Francis, 03/16/1962 -06/19/1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Clark, Kenneth H., 02/09/1995 -10/28/1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cohen, Phillip, 12/16/1974 -01/23/1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cole, Carmella A., 10/16/1987 -08/23/1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cooperman, Benjamin, 02/13/1997 -09/11/1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cortina, Mauricio, 10/27/1994 -02/04/1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Coruzzi, Marilyn C., 10/01/1993 -11/20/1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Coyne, Patrick A., 12/19/1977 -07/05/1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Craig, Eileen, 10/27/1994 -08/27/1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Daly, Jane M., 01/18/1990 -03/17/1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Daniels, Herman, 01/25/1991 -06/18/1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Datch, Michael W., 03/19/1987 -11/26/1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - DeToledo, Joao C., 02/10/1994 -02/06/1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - DiValentin, Louis L., 07/19/1996 -02/18/1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Doman, David B., 10/15/1981 -03/07/1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Duncan, Conrad J., 10/27/1994 -08/15/1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Eager, Anne, 06/17/1975 -12/27/1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Ebuwei, Regina C., NP, 01/16/1992 -08/25/1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Department: Anesthesiology
  - Eng, Gloria, 12/15/1969 -06/18/1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fabian, William, 01/15/1987 -06/02/1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fairbanks, David, 12/20/1976 -02/26/1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Feinman, Mitchell, 05/07/1993 -08/30/1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Feldman, Irvin, 03/27/1946 -06/26/1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Ferebee, Nancy S., 10/16/1986 -10/23/1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fletcher, Anne B., 12/18/1972 -10/01/1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Fogel, Julius, 07/30/1946 -02/04/1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fortune, Ulla M., 12/21/1970 -01/18/1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Department: Orthopaedic Surgery
  - Fox, Harold, 02/08/1996 -11/01/1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fox, Mary R., 06/15/1975 -03/11/1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Frey, Linda, 10/17/1991 -06/19/1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Friedman, Herbert N., 10/16/1980 -01/16/1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Friedman, Roger J., 10/20/1985 -06/18/1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Frishberg, Benhamin M., 10/17/1985 -08/01/1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Frost, Andra R., 10/17/1991 -06/15/1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Department: Pathology
  - Gaarder, Kenneth R., 09/15/1980 -12/05/1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Garcia, Julio E., 05/07/1993 -06/30/1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Department: Radiology
  - Garvey, Carol, 05/15/1997 -09/05/1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Department: Health Care Sciences
  - Ghezzi, Keith T., 01/21/1988 -05/15/1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Gibbs, Neville A., 10/15/1987 -06/23/1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Glassman, Bruce D., 10/01/1994 -03/11/1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Department: Dermatology
  - Gorbea, Enrique T., 07/01/1994 -06/30/1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Gray, Luther W., 10/03/1979 -11/19/1996 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Halista, Kevin D., 09/01/1995 -06/30/1996 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hamburger, David P., 06/18/1979 -06/27/1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Harviel, Jay D., 10/28/1983 -06/20/1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Heller, Naomi, 05/17/1979 -03/10/1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Herzig, Michael, 10/28/1993 -07/11/1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hessler, Richard B., 10/27/1994 -08/31/1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hilkert, Fred G., 02/15/1963 -12/12/1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Holen, Sheldon, 03/21/1967 -04/16/1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Honig, Jacqueline R., 02/08/1996 -05/09/1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hudson, Edwin R., 10/26/1995 -05/03/1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hugh, Violet B., 01/15/1974 -06/30/1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Isaason, Norman, 06/09/1952 -03/23/1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jarrett, Thomas, 07/07/1995 -09/30/1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Department: Urology
  - Jaslow, David, 02/08/1996 -06/30/1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Department: Emergency Medicine
  - Javedan, Mehrdad, 04/03/1972 -01/14/1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Jerome, Marc A., 12/20/1996 -09/25/1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Edward L., 02/10/1993 -01/13/1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Jr., Paul W., 09/17/1979 -07/09/1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Mark, 09/06/1996 -09/01/1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Joshi, Rajendra G., 05/12/1995 -08/04/1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Kalunian, Douglas A., 10/28/1993 -07/01/1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Karr, Sharon, 10/28/1993 -08/04/1997 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Karr, Stewart B., 10/17/1991 -01/23/1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Kasloff, Ilene M., 10/28/1993 -02/26/1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Health Care Sciences
  - Katikineni, Mangal, 10/16/1980 -02/24/1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kay, Stephen R., 03/01/1987 -03/17/1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Keegan, Michael T., 10/17/1991 -01/29/1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kent, Stephen G., 09/01/1967 -05/15/1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Kerr, Lindsey, 10/28/1993 -06/19/1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Kim, Chul, 10/01/1988 -12/01/1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Kim, Nancy C., 08/01/1979 -06/30/1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - King, Lawrence, 03/18/1974 -09/09/1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Kirsch, Claudia, 03/09/1996 -08/20/1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Kleinerman, Deena, 01/18/1990 -03/20/1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Knaus, William A., 07/01/1995 -10/31/1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Koch, Edward G., 12/18/1978 -10/31/1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Korengold, Marvin C., 05/09/1955 -02/03/1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Kurzrok, Neal M., 05/18/1989 -07/01/1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Kuzmowych, Truvor, 05/17/1979 -04/11/1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lando, Howard M., 02/10/1994 -06/10/1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Landy, Helain J., 02/08/1996 -06/30/1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Lauredo, Robert, 12/19/1977 -05/06/1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Lee, A. Gail, 10/28/1993 -01/13/1997 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Lem, Diana S., 10/26/1995 -04/21/1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Levin, Barry J., 10/18/1979 -06/19/1997 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Litman, Deborah S., 03/19/1992 -06/06/1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Litvan, Irene, 02/09/1995 -09/01/1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Luban, Norman A., 12/19/1997 -08/26/1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Lustberg, Thomas J., 03/20/1980 -04/16/1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - MacDonald-Ginzburg, 10/18/1979 -10/22/1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mann, Marcy D., 02/10/1994 -06/05/1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mann, Peter C.C., 10/15/1992 -01/01/1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Margolis, Richard S., 09/15/1975 -12/02/1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Marks, Zana H., 10/27/1994 -12/17/1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Markus, Nancy R., 05/01/1996 -08/22/1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Masri-Fridling, Gayle D., 02/14/1994 -09/13/1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Masterson, Richard S., 02/10/1994 -03/20/1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Matsumoto, Maria A., 07/01/1994 -06/30/1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Mazonson, Anne C., 01/25/1991 -01/22/1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - McGowan, Larry, 12/15/1969 -12/10/1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - McKenzie, Diane F., 06/16/1987 -08/24/1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - McKnew Jr., Donald H., 12/16/1968 -02/03/1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - McMarlin, Stacy L., 02/10/1994 -01/31/1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Meister, Stephen J., 07/06/1994 -06/30/1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Meyers, Barbara, 06/19/1975 -08/15/1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Miller, Glenn, 06/19/1978 -06/19/1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Miller, Valery T., 03/20/1980 -05/01/1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Miotto, Peter J., 02/09/1995 -09/07/1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Moreyra, Eduardo, 05/15/1997 -06/14/1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Morgan, Seth A., 06/01/1987 -06/30/1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Mrose, Helen, 09/01/1992 -08/27/1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Mukherjee, Diane C., 10/28/1993 -02/06/1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Neuberger, Frank W., 10/17/1966 -11/26/1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Noble, Raymond A., 10/17/1991 -01/28/1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Nochomovitz, Lucien E., 05/19/1980 -06/15/1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ocuin, Esther, 01/15/1987 -03/08/1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Olshaker, Bennett, 08/07/1950 -02/20/1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - O'Malley, Sean, 02/01/1995 -07/01/1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Department: Neurological Surgery
  - Oni, Ayokunle A., 02/09/1995 -05/01/1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Orleans, Ronald J., 09/01/1975 -12/02/1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ostrzenski, Adam, 10/15/1987 -06/01/1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Ott, John E., 09/17/1989 -01/01/1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Palmon Jr., Florentine P., 03/15/1965 -03/27/1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Parrot, Robert H., 03/19/1973 -08/19/1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Perlin, Seymour, 06/16/1975 -10/29/1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Perman, Gerald, 10/15/1981 -07/08/1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Pincetl, Pierre, 06/16/1975 -10/24/1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Pradad, Uma, 10/19/1989 -09/29/1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Rabin, Karen, 10/30/1995 -07/31/1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Raizon, Arnold, 10/17/1991 -11/03/1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Rao, Vikram, 07/01/1995 -08/02/1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Redd, Jacquelyn, 02/09/1995 -11/17/1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Redjaee, Bahram, 03/19/1992 -04/01/1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Reisin, Jorge H., 06/18/1994 -07/19/1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Department: Surgery/Plastic
  - Richard, Robert, 12/22/1995 -06/30/1996 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Department: Neurosurgery
  - Rickler, Kenneth C., 10/01/1990 -04/05/1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Riedel, Charles J., 01/16/1992 -09/16/1997 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Robinson, Joseph R., 10/28/1993 -01/17/1997 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Rokoske, Leslie D., 02/08/1996 -03/03/1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rose, Myron, 06/18/1987 -03/14/1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Rosenbaum, Stephen, 01/17/1980 -03/17/1997 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Ross, David S., 10/18/1984 -07/10/1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Saladino, Lawrence P., 10/27/1994 -06/30/1996 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - SamTani, Sameer, 07/01/1995 -08/02/1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Sandmeyer, Melvin, 07/02/1957 -04/01/1996 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Schoettler, James A., 09/23/1968 -05/30/1997 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Schreiber, Julius, 07/11/1949 -02/24/1997 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Schulte, Brian P., 03/01/1993 -09/30/1996 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Department: Family Practice
  - Schwab, Fredrick J., 05/19/1988 -12/26/1996 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Scully, James H., 10/27/1994 -12/16/1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Shapiro, Jerome, 10/17/1985 -03/01/1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Sharma, Meeta B., 10/28/1993 -08/27/1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Shawl, Fayaz A., 03/19/1992 -04/16/1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Shay, Peter A., 11/24/1991 -03/31/1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Shayani, Vaga, 02/08/1996 -06/30/1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sherman, Mark E., 10/27/1994 -12/15/1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Shimm, Peter B., 10/24/1996 -07/16/1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Shrier, Diane K., 02/09/1995 -06/30/1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Shuaib, Ashfog, 10/24/1996 -07/16/1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Silbergleit, Robert, 02/20/1996 -07/01/1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Silby, Howard, 12/15/1969 -01/12/1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Silverberg, Steven, 10/21/1982 -08/02/1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Sims, Dodd A., 03/20/1986 -08/20/1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Sislen, Maurice A., 08/10/1953 -03/10/1997 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Howard N., 10/20/1988 -03/07/1997 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Lee E., 01/19/1984 -08/29/1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Smoller, Bruce M., 12/20/1976 -12/24/1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Sokas, Rosmary, 01/18/1990 -01/20/1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Solomon, Herbert M., 12/01/1968 -11/26/1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Stark, Karen, 02/10/1994 -09/01/1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Stark, William, 02/09/1953 -12/16/1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Steren, Moises N., 12/01/1982 -11/15/1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Stern, Harvey J., 06/20/1988 -12/01/1995 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Stevens, Harold, 10/16/1945 -12/06/1995 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Stewart, Eleanor S., 02/09/1995 -08/01/1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Department: Medicine/HCS
  - Stewart, Jr., Steele F., 09/19/1964 -02/10/1997 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Strassburger, Terri, 05/15/1997 -07/01/1997 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Svoboda, Jeff T., 05/01/1993 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Teno, Joan, 05/16/1996 -09/30/1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Jason, 08/26/1996 -12/01/1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Titer, Evadne M., 12/17/1973 -10/23/1996 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Department: Ophthalmology Surgery
  - Trad, Karim S., 10/15/1992 -09/14/1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Tyau, Laurie S. Y., 02/15/1994 -08/26/1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    epartment: Ob/Gyn
  - Uro, Philip J., 10/11/1990 -04/01/1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Visus, Maria, 05/06/1994 -07/23/1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Von Albertini, Beat, 10/16/1986 -05/11/1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Wagman, Bernard M., 10/11/1990 -01/03/1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Wallace, William D., 02/16/1968 -11/11/1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Weinberger, Daniel, 01/17/1980 -08/26/1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Weintraub, Herbert, 09/20/1971 -09/20/1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Welch, Laura S., 01/15/1987 -07/04/1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Whipple, Katherine, 10/15/1992 -12/27/1996 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Widra, Eric A., 10/27/1994 -06/30/1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Witorsch, Philip, 05/18/1979 -06/05/1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Wohlgmuth, Caroline W., 07/01/1993 -02/10/1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Wolin, Steven J., 09/25/1972 -01/05/1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Yeager, Amy, 10/27/1994 -12/01/1997 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Young, Robert, 07/01/1985 -03/17/1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Zinner, John, 12/20/1973 -03/17/1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Inactive physicians files, 1949-1997; RG0007 Series 13; 9 Linear feet
  - Quattlebaum, James T., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Quintana, Fidel J., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - R-Love, John w., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rabinowitz, Seymour, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rabkin, Boris, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Racy, Anis, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Radice, Luis C., undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Raffel, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Raja, Gopol, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ramsey, Herbert Percy, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Rand, Anna T., undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Randall, Sanford Jay, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Randolph, Judson, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rankin, Joseph E., undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rannings, Dolores A., undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rao, Kosarju, R., undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rao, Narsing, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Rapee, Lawrence A., undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Raphael, Gordon, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ratcliffe, Harold, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ratner, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Rattan, Pawah K., undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Raver, James M., undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ray, Enos, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Rayford, Linwood, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Razi, Ahmad, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Rea, Edward L., undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Reba, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Recinos, Adrian Jr., undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rees, Thomas, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Reeves, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - William Reff, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Regan, Robert M., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Reich, Joel J., undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Remy, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Renfield, Marilyn L., undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Renshaw, Josephine E., undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Renzi. Gerald, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Resnik, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Reuter, Frederick T., undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Reyes, Pauline, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Reynolds, Donald C., undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Reynolds, Royal, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Rheingold, Jack, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Rice, Katherine K., undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Rich, Jeffery I., undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Richardson, Francis X., undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Richardson Jr., Henry B., undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Richman, Joseph H., undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Richman, Sanford N., undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Richmond, Marion B., undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Richtmeyer, Duane Case, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Richwine, Alfred H., undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Richwine, Barton Winters, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Riddick, Leroy, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Riddle, Patrick J., undated (Box 1, Folder 56)